imglobal.me 2014-02-13

# Imglobal Online Marketing System

Our Privacy Policy

IMGlobal.me is committed to protecting the privacy of our online visitors and community. We collect information from online visitors who ask to be on our newsletter mailing list and/or receive periodic email announcements. Anyone who wishes can choose to be removed from our mailing list at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any email.

In addition, online visitors who wish to purchase a membership through our Web site must provide their name, email address, mailing address, phone number, and credit card number and expiration date. All credit card transactions occur over a secure connection and third party processor and no credit card details are kept or stored by IMGlobal.me.

All online visitor data collected by IMGlobal.me is protected against unauthorized access. We will not sell, trade, or give your personal information to other companies or organisations.

Database Integrity

IMglobal and employee will never solicit any of our community members leads, members or personal database for any reason. Our community is only built around growing your brand and Business online. Our databases are secured by Bank standard 256 SSL encryption and our servers are fully managed and monitored real time 24/7/365 for any security threats.

Children’s Privacy

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems. IMGlobal.me encourages parents to go online with their kids. Here are a few tips to help make a child\\\\\\\\\\\\\'s online experience safer:

Teach kids never to give personal information, unless supervised by a parent or responsible adult. Includes name, address, phone, school, etc.  
Know the sites your kids are visiting and which sites are appropriate.  
Look for Web site privacy policies. Know how your child\\\\\\\\\\\\\'s information is treated.  
Check out the FTC\\\\\\\\\\\\\'s site for more tips on protecting children\\\\\\\\\\\\\'s privacy online

Contacting Us:

IMGlobal Marketing Community  
Level 13, 50 Cavill Avenue  
Surfers Paradise,  
Gold Coast   
Australia 4217

Phone: 07 5635 4333  
E-mail: support@IMGlobal.me

UK  
72 High Street,   
Haslemere,   
Surrey,   
GU27 2LA
